Rahmat Abdulfattah

Frontend developer with experience in creating visually appealing and user-friendly websites. Strong problem-solving skills and the ability to translate designs into functional and responsive interfaces

Agege Lagos,NIgeria +(234) 9042129208 omobowalerohma1998@gmai l.com

Github: <u>veiled-coder</u> LinkedIn: <u>Rahmah</u> Abdulfattah

Portfolio: veiled-coder

EXPERIENCE

Zuri Internship, Remote — frontend developer

OCT 2022 - NOV 2022

- Implemented Form Validation Using React Hooks For State Management
- Built Website Using React Library
- Implemented Context Api To Avoid Prop Drilling
- React Hooks For Modal Pop-Up And Hamburger Menu
- React Router Dom For Website Page Navigation

Tech Stack: Javascript, Css, React.Js, Html, Bootstrap

SideHustle Internship, Remote — frontend developer

OCT 2021 - DEC 2021

- Collaborated With A Team Of Frontend Developers To Build A Learning Management System Using Git As Version Control
- Built The Sign-Up And Login Forms (Admin & Students) And User's Profile, Email Confirmation And Password Reset Pages
- Implemented Responsiveness On Mobile And Desktop Screens Using Css Positioning & Flexbox

Tech Stack: Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap

EDUCATION

LAGOS STATE UNIVERSITY, Ojo Lagos — Chemistry

DEC 2016 - MARCH 2022

SheCodes Bootcamp, Remote — Frontend development

JULY 2022 - PRESENT

- Javascript Dom Manipulation
- Rest Api (fetch data with axios)
- Responsive Web Design (Bootstrap & Css) and SEO

SKILLS

Languages: Html, Css, Javascript.

Frameworks/ Libraries: Bootstrap, React.js, Ajax

Others: Web accessibility, Ajax, Dom manipulation, Responsive Web design, Consuming REST APIS.

LANGUAGES

English(Professional)

Yoruba (Native)

PROJECTS

<u>Watweather</u> — A responsive web application that displays real-time weather information, weather forecast and time of cities around the world

Tech Stack: Html, Css, Javascript, Rest Api, Geolocation Api

<u>Mylintree</u> — A responsive web application that allows users link to their social media handles and get feedback from client through a form

Tech Stack: Css, React.Js, React Hooks, React-Router-Dom

<u>Metabnb</u> — A responsive website displaying meta accommodation

Tech Stack: React.Js, React Hooks, React-Router-Dom, Css Grid And Flexbox